Greg Mrowczynski

Web Developer

Creative, detail-oriented Frontend Web Developer, with proven team work and problem solving experience, gained in various roles and environments, during over 15 years of professional career, mainly in manufacturing and engineering. Since end of 2021 I've been learning, practicing and working as freelance Web Developer. Hard skills include JavaScript, React, Typescript, Nodejs, testing and debugging. Thanks to soft skills developed during my education and professional career, I can easily adapt to new environments and different programming languages. I enjoy picking up new skills in the pursuit of self-improvement.

Work History

2022-02 -Current

Frontend Developer

Freelance, Nuneaton

I've been Individually learning and practicing coding and web development. I have worked on web design projects for few individuals, with use of frontend technologies: JavaScript, React, CSS. In them projects I communicated with clients during development process, to confirm creative proposals, and design best practices. I also rebuilt one client's site, initially written in HTML/CSS, using React.

Sample of my projects (available on my personal page gregmdev.co.uk):

- Movie tickets booking page (with use of local storage)
- Exchange Rate Calculator (Rest API)
- Slot machine (Object Oriented Programming)

2022-04 -2022-12

Quality Engineer

LEVC, Coventry

- Participated in multi-disciplinary defect reviews to discern and address root causes.
- Supported quality team members during corrective action updates.
- Facilitated process improvements to successfully

Contact

Address

Nuneaton

Phone

07492204194

E-mail

greg19850@gmail.com

www

www.gregmdev.co.uk

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/gregmrowczynski

Technical Profile

- JavaScript
- React.is
- TypeScript
- HTML
- CSS
- Node.is
- MongoDB
- PostgreSQL
- Express.js
- Jest
- SASS/SCSS
- Bootstrap
- REST API
- JSON
- Git
- GitHub

Competencies

Front End Web Development decrease errors.

 Suppliers PPAP weekly approval rate increased by 200% (from 2 to 6)

2018-09 - Quality Engineer

IMK Automotive, Coventry

- Led problem-solving activities to quickly identify and permanently resolve quality and productivity issues. Reduced customer issues amount by 20% in 2 years
- Cost of quality reduced by 30 % in first year, and another 20% in year 2
- 100% of PPAP's for new projects sent in time to customers
- Completing 8D's average time reduced from 28 to 14 days.
- Developed traceability documentation to aid in investigating faults and defects.
- Supported quality team members during corrective action updates.
- Built strong rapport with team members, management and clients to facilitate efficiency and productivity.

2015-07 - Quality Technician

2018-08

2022-04

LISI Aerospace, Rugby

- Performed thorough inspections of incoming materials and outgoing products.
- Evaluated conformance of products with quality standards.
- Generated detailed reports outlining results and recommendations.

2015-01 - CNC Machine Operator

2015-07 Lawrence Automotive, Coventry

2012-12 - Machine Operator

2015-01 IMK Automotive, Coventry

Education

2007-09 - MBA: Applied Mathematics

2011-11

Warsaw School of Business And Int. Finances -Warsaw, Poland Programming

Website design

Troubleshooting

Programming Languages

Standard-compliant coding

Responsive design

Languages

Polish

2000-09 -2004-06

High School Diploma

Edward Dembowski High School No. 1 - Zielona Gora, Poland

Interests

Reading Books

Gym /Healthy lifestyle

Films